<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2016-01-13T18:00:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Try to Understand, He's a Magic Man!</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/try-to-understand-hes-a-magic-man/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/try-to-understand-hes-a-magic-man/</id>
    <published>2016-01-13T18:00:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-15T00:13:44-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;figure class="figure figure--right"&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" width="360" height="252" src="/diaryland/assets/images/crystals-96b51c4a.jpg" /&gt;  &lt;figcaption class="figure__caption"&gt;Crystal's Pizza, Abilene, TX&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There was, and still is, a magician&lt;/strong&gt; called Lonnie Chevrie who used to perform at Crystal’s Pizza &amp;amp; Spaghetti in the 90s. My parents knew him. The Smith children loved him. &lt;a href="http://www.lonniechevrie.com/Site/Welcome.html"&gt;He has a website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tending to the Compost Heap</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/tending-to-the-compost-heap/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/tending-to-the-compost-heap/</id>
    <published>2015-11-20T18:00:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-14T22:49:47-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well I woke up early&lt;/strong&gt; and the dog through the backyard window was chewing on a hackberry branch. I lay prostrate in bed, farting quietly into the sleeping bag and watching spiders float in transverse waves over the compost pile when I found myself plodding down a road of unhappy thinking. So I rose, shampoo’d, and chased Henry throughout the great backyard with a bowl of apple’n’oatmeal in my hand. Henry reared on his hind legs and swung a branch in his mouth around like a quarterstaff, appearing at the same time like a horse and its rider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="figure figure--left"&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" width="800" height="800" src="/diaryland/assets/images/craft-show-ea21230b.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way to Cherrywood, a plastic yard sign pointed towards a craft fair held at the autumnal Presbyterian church, set in ledgestone, just over there, at the top of a grassy slope. I approached. Upon entry, a silvery old woman in an applique vest cooed sweet greetings to me, her eyes just visible between a display of plastic wreaths. I approached. She pointed out some of her wares: salad spoons and soaps coddled in linen drawstring bags. She gestured grandly towards a folding table on the far side of the room, creaking under the bounty of a hundred denim-clad church lady–hours: hard cookies, monkey bread, pumpkin rolls, styrofoam coffee, blintzes, puffs, and wheels. I approached. A genteel big-haired woman from Lago Vista woo’d me to her table with ornate descriptions of her scented candles. She explained she was more of a musk lady than a floral one. Couldn’t stand the scent of Jasmine. I liked Rocky Mountain Christmas and told her so. Handed her some money. Went on my way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the names of all the available WiFi networks as I sit here at this peeling picnic table:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class="list--pretty"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;belkin.2.4&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;All Hail Our Dark Father Satan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Leia is LITERALLY Hitler&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rock Hard Vagina&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;that’s rich&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;So Fresh So Clean&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Netgear78&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Netgear46&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;veronicas equinox&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sopping Wet Balls&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TWCWiFi&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;thatsacuteweiner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Green Sunset</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/green-sunset/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/green-sunset/</id>
    <published>2015-10-24T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-14T23:14:57-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Green Sunset is a smoothie&lt;/strong&gt; I get at Juice Land. It’s the color of a canyon, mauve and orange and cherry red, with flecks of black vegetable, and I love it! Next to the register rests an opalescent crystal the size of a Nerf football. One of the juice-goons employed there once saw me looking at it and said something about how humans find crystals appealing because they express the ease with which nature generates beautiful morphologies and adapts to change. I didn’t understand what he meant, but I appreciated the word “morphology.” He had a pony tail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It rained on the way home, a little, and the smell of burgers was in the air.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Vermin Supreme</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/vermin-supreme/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/vermin-supreme/</id>
    <published>2015-10-23T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-14T23:57:56-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I was slouching at the bus stop&lt;/strong&gt; in front of the state capital when an old dude flopped on the bench next to me and started narrating what he saw to himself in a husky southern drawl, quiety, under his breath. He said: “So many birds!” as a hundred or more flew overhead in a soft patter of wings. “I’ve lived here nearly all my life and…and still what a day!” I looked over. He had bucked teeth, like a wild rodent, and cowboy stubble, and a tucked-in denim shirt. His legs were crossed like two noodles and his hair drifted around like wisps over a soup bowl. His eyes browsed the street scene. Two trailing birds flew overhead. “Look! There are two of em!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crosswalk sign flashed and the man made of brilliant white LEDs morphed into numbers counting down. “8, 7, 6” the guy said, following the numbers one step behind. He counted all the way down to zero until the red hand appeared, flashing. Having come to the conclusion of this little story, he looked out again over the street, seemingly pleased with how it had concluded. He turned to me: “I’ve been on the 5th floor of that building.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know there’s someone running for president named “Vermin Supreme?” And that we wears a boot on his head?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  A man without a dinosaur is like a tree without a branch. Ha! Ha! Ain't no real tree!
  &lt;cite&gt;Man on the bus with a 1 gallon ziplock bag on his lap filled with cantaloupe and honeydew.&lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Afternoon Cake</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/afternoon-cake/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/afternoon-cake/</id>
    <published>2015-08-24T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-14T23:37:12-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I got a piece of chocolate cake in the afternoon&lt;/strong&gt;, on the bottom floor of an old-timey hotel downtown. It had a flake of real gold on it and it also cost $9 (which is a lot of money, if you ask me, for a bit of cake). I walked back in the sun to the office and ate it in front of the computer screen at work. I ate the flake of gold too. The coffee was gross smelled like the way my old car used to smell after a rain storm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned that in 2014, a collosal statue was found in Egypt depicting Agamemnon III the Magnificent and  his wife, Tiye, seated side-by-side “with three of their daughters standing in front of the throne—Henuttaneb, the largest and best preserved, in the centre; Nebetah on the right; and another, whose name is destroyed, on the left.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="figure figure--full"&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" width="634" height="390" src="/diaryland/assets/images/agamemnoniii-f87347eb.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Technology Deacon</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/technology-deacon/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/technology-deacon/</id>
    <published>2015-06-29T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-14T23:52:28-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I learned today that my dad is the technology deacon at his church.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
