<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-11-20T18:00:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Tending to the Compost Heap</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/tending-to-the-compost-heap/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/tending-to-the-compost-heap/</id>
    <published>2015-11-20T18:00:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-14T22:49:47-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well I woke up early&lt;/strong&gt; and the dog through the backyard window was chewing on a hackberry branch. I lay prostrate in bed, farting quietly into the sleeping bag and watching spiders float in transverse waves over the compost pile when I found myself plodding down a road of unhappy thinking. So I rose, shampoo’d, and chased Henry throughout the great backyard with a bowl of apple’n’oatmeal in my hand. Henry reared on his hind legs and swung a branch in his mouth around like a quarterstaff, appearing at the same time like a horse and its rider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="figure figure--left"&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" width="800" height="800" src="/diaryland/assets/images/craft-show-fc784728.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way to Cherrywood, a plastic yard sign pointed towards a craft fair held at the autumnal Presbyterian church, set in ledgestone, just over there, at the top of a grassy slope. I approached. Upon entry, a silvery old woman in an applique vest cooed sweet greetings to me, her eyes just visible between a display of plastic wreaths. I approached. She pointed out some of her wares: salad spoons and soaps coddled in linen drawstring bags. She gestured grandly towards a folding table on the far side of the room, creaking under the bounty of a hundred denim-clad church lady–hours: hard cookies, monkey bread, pumpkin rolls, styrofoam coffee, blintzes, puffs, and wheels. I approached. A genteel big-haired woman from Lago Vista woo’d me to her table with ornate descriptions of her scented candles. She explained she was more of a musk lady than a floral one. Couldn’t stand the scent of Jasmine. I liked Rocky Mountain Christmas and told her so. Handed her some money. Went on my way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the names of all the available WiFi networks as I sit here at this peeling picnic table:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class="list--pretty"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;belkin.2.4&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;All Hail Our Dark Father Satan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Leia is LITERALLY Hitler&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rock Hard Vagina&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;that’s rich&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;So Fresh So Clean&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Netgear78&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Netgear46&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;veronicas equinox&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sopping Wet Balls&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TWCWiFi&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;thatsacuteweiner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Environmental Sounds</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/environmental-sounds/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/environmental-sounds/</id>
    <published>2008-08-28T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-01-03T23:41:08-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last night Gelber came over&lt;/strong&gt; to the house to pick up a few things he had left after he moved. We were talking in the living room about whatever when it started to rain. This was a bad thing because it meant Gelber couldn’t leave yet. This was also a good thing because the house was full of cardboard boxes and bare floors and only me, and rain meant that Gelber couldn’t leave yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We found one of Billy’s vinyls that said in large green letters, &lt;strong&gt;NATURE’S MUSIC…RECORDED ON THIS PLANET&lt;/strong&gt;, a field recording of a thunderstorm, and thought it would be funny to put it on while the real thunderstorm was flashing about outside. It was pretty funny for a while; we made gin &amp;amp; tonics and walked around on the carpet. It was extra real. It was 3D. But then it suddenly became profane what we were doing, listening to a reproduction while the original storm had been given to us freely. It seemed terrible. The Grandfathers of the Lokota Sioux should have swooped down from the sky on their crimson steeds weilding lightning bolts in their fists! They should have spoken in terrible voices through their dog masks at us, &lt;strong&gt;DEFILERS! TAKE THAT VINYL AND SMASH IT ON THE CLIFF BELOW! YOU MUST NOT PROFANE THE THUNDERSTORM!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="figure figure--right figure--vertical"&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" width="432" height="640" src="/diaryland/assets/images/ludwig-koch-49699b08.jpg" /&gt;  &lt;figcaption class="figure__caption"&gt;Ludwig Koch&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news, our house in Fishtown is haunted by a woman named Claire. UPS delievered a package here when nobody was home, and a woman named Claire signed for it who supposedly lives three doors to the left. But when we got back, &lt;strong&gt;THE PACKAGE WAS SITTING IN THE MIDDLE OF OUR LIVING ROOM FLOOR&lt;/strong&gt;. How could the package get in the house if the doors were locked? Claire. Further proof is found in an unusual occurance that both Mike and Billy have witnessed first hand concerning a borrowed yellow bicycle with a banana seat which sits in the living room. On two different occassions, the bicycle’s bell was heard ringing &lt;strong&gt;ALL BY ITSELF&lt;/strong&gt; in the living room even though nobody else was home. How could the bicycle’s bell ring if nobody was in the living room? Claire. There have also been the sounds of screaming outside our windows, glass bottles flying through the air, and the sounds of babies crying somewhere far away, although we can hardly blame Claire for that; it’s just another day in Fishtown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite thing that I frequently hear some lady yelling to her kids in the gravely, blown-out voice of an Eagles fan is: &lt;strong&gt;NO MORE STREET, YA HEAR ME! NO MORE STREET!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Octopus</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/the-octopus/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/the-octopus/</id>
    <published>2003-08-07T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2015-12-04T00:07:26-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;a story of miami&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;setting&lt;/strong&gt;: open-air country, california. 20th century ad&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CAST&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;dr. scholls:&lt;/strong&gt; mitchum gansby&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; stephen segal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fox:&lt;/strong&gt; the fox&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;old woman no. 1:&lt;/strong&gt; mabel guthrie&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;old woman no. 2:&lt;/strong&gt; cloe elaine green&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; thom yorke&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the cuban:&lt;/strong&gt; peter malsteem&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the president of a company:&lt;/strong&gt; lance neuhouser&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the parish priest:&lt;/strong&gt; david ratliff&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the holy ghost:&lt;/strong&gt; the holy ghost&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the shark:&lt;/strong&gt; fabrizio moretti&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the jellyfish:&lt;/strong&gt; a jellyfish&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the seahorse:&lt;/strong&gt; michael stipe&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the boy:&lt;/strong&gt; sebastian palmeri&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the girl:&lt;/strong&gt; audrey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the guest:&lt;/strong&gt; albert camus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the octopus:&lt;/strong&gt; an octopus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a voice:&lt;/strong&gt; though the scene is alive, all is silent and sleeping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; an enormous crowd is gathered in the streets of a slum in central miami. children and adults fill the streets, all in rags. burlap rags. a smoke screen hovers over the masses. an office building looks down. signs of protest. the throng becomes ravenous. the crowd becomes violent. they pump their fists into the black sky and scream with words that no man can hear. all is hush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a voice:&lt;/strong&gt; slowly, slowly the sound of laughter arises. it is not normal laughter, but irritating laughter, like that kind of laugh that someone makes when he has no confidence in his own humor. the sounds of static pink-noise fills up the theatre. timpani rolls. the house symphony swells in with a final deafening chord.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; a microphone slowly descends from the stage as the curtains close. it is covered in a fuzzy wind screen. all is silent again. the cast comes out from either side of the stage and the curtains pull up again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a voice:&lt;/strong&gt; the octopus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;dr. scholls:&lt;/strong&gt; i am sitting here in a white chair in my sun-room. it is nearing evening. this is the setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; dr. scholls sips on a frosty cup of iced tree. he is wearing yellow shorts and a white t-shirt with no sleeves. white hair is on his chest like steel-wool from heaven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; good afternoon, dr. scholls. i have your order right here in my hands. what are you reading? it is a beautiful day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;dr. scholls:&lt;/strong&gt; it will rain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; i am wearing a white smock and a white cap that says milk in red letters. but it is such a beautiful day. what could happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; both of the characters freeze and the light from the balcony is moved to a painted scene outside, where a young boy and a young girl are playing in a sprinkler. the grass is a most delicious shade of green. a falcon comes from the clouds and takes the little girl in his claws. her head is found many months later by the boy in a toy box covered with dried blood and chocolate syrup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; i have been swimming today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;old woman 1:&lt;/strong&gt; now we are at the house by the side of the road, where weary travelers let down their load. welcome, stranger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the guest:&lt;/strong&gt; we are in a house under the coming clouds. it is weather-beaten, but loved. several people converse cordially in the living area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;old woman 1:&lt;/strong&gt; old woman 2, we have a new guest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;old woman 2:&lt;/strong&gt; old woman 1 and old woman 2 are both dressed in the fashion of the old days, each carrying several layers of lip-stick on their faces. they smell of sweet perfume and soaps. their house has lace and wicker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;knight:&lt;/strong&gt; welcome, weary traveler. unladen thine physique of burdens and metaphysical sorrows. here, let me pinch thee in the behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; the night pinches the guest in the behind most prestigiously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;old woman 1:&lt;/strong&gt; you are in luck, guest. we are having butt-cakes and hot tree for a change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fox:&lt;/strong&gt; i am a fox, and the old woman’s pet. i helped aldous huxley write his book on contemporary literary criticism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a voice:&lt;/strong&gt; the rain clouds are coming over the horizon, and the sun is backed into the back of the theater stage. the wind picks up and synthesized wind comes whistling from the window panes. it grows dark outside.
(a cuban and the parish priest enter the doorway with sacks of snorkels and goggles)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;dr. scholls:&lt;/strong&gt; i have made an appointment with the hair parlor. they say he works wonders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ms. bells:&lt;/strong&gt; i have heard that nobody does a better job of cutting the hair than the parish priest himself!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;parish priest:&lt;/strong&gt; and here i am. with no scissors. they must be in my automobile.
(time passes slowly for delinquents. the excitement of the coming weekends dawns as the storm approaches)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ms. apples:&lt;/strong&gt; milkman, may i hold your hand?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; (flirt)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ms. apples:&lt;/strong&gt; you give me too much credit. how agreeable your features are to me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; (flirt)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ms. apples:&lt;/strong&gt; may i hold your hand in mine?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;priest:&lt;/strong&gt; (whispering) walk away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; there is a sudden glorious harp frill that erupts from center stage. the entire cast is filled with awe and all begin to talk excitedly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;cuban:&lt;/strong&gt; i am amazed at the sounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; i feel thee in my soul.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;holy ghost:&lt;/strong&gt; can you see me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;c.e.o:&lt;/strong&gt; and that was how i came to fall for the minstrel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;boy:&lt;/strong&gt; my youth is a plague.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;girl:&lt;/strong&gt; your youth and mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;dr. scholls:&lt;/strong&gt; is that so? even my shoe-comforters could not fathom this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;c.e.o:&lt;/strong&gt; your furniture resembles artifacts of ancient suburbia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the guest:&lt;/strong&gt; where are the butt-cakes and hot tree?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; come here, my beautiful porpoise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ms. apples:&lt;/strong&gt; i am like a radiant beam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a voice:&lt;/strong&gt; the house is now underwater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; the sound of underwater submarines is heard all over the house. stephen segal, which is me, is now hovering from the rafters in a golfing uniform holding a microphone. the symphony keeps the beat of his heart with a timpani drum and a waterphone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;boy:&lt;/strong&gt; i see the lights from the surface show very dimly here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;girl:&lt;/strong&gt; yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;octopus:&lt;/strong&gt; it is not a bad life. meet my friends who live in this sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; octopus, jellyfish, seahorse, shark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ms. apples:&lt;/strong&gt; i am aflame with lust. please direct me to the salad bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;milkman:&lt;/strong&gt; (flirt)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;octopus:&lt;/strong&gt; i will now dismember your soul in order to keep you silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;dr. scholls:&lt;/strong&gt; my liquid comforters keep every sole happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; a white light erupts from the bottom of the ocean and all is white. the sounds of chirstmas carols being played backwards, marching armies, korg synthesizer, japanese keyboards, feedback, microphone hissing, and static-electricity from carpet feed slowly into the stage. suddenly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a voice:&lt;/strong&gt; men in white sheets like ghosts come tied to ropes from the ceiling and take all the mens’ hats in the auditorium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;narrator:&lt;/strong&gt; the sounds become louder. and louder. it is unbearable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;boy:&lt;/strong&gt; (standing up from the ocean floor and pointing out to the audience) look. a drum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a voice:&lt;/strong&gt; nervous laughter swells up from back stage.
(the curtain closes and the symphony gives one last deafening chord before the entire audience begins to leave.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;END&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Night</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/the-night/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/the-night/</id>
    <published>2003-08-07T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2015-12-04T00:01:03-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;an imaginary essay written by air-conditioner&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It is the night&lt;/strong&gt; that fills in the marshes of the sun, the night that comes in streams and circles into the deep planet, green and dark, that imbues the crests of creation with dream. The day has its specific charm noted infrequently in its transient passage through the white morning curtains, but if truth is to be told, it is only at night when the verve of life comes out of the water and enjoys a beverage beside the pool. It begins as you step through the door, out of the wicker house. There it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is there as it has always been there. It is a lonesome miser who lives in the company of yellow newspaper, televisions, iodine bottles, who sits on furniture and gazes out the window as you and your sister throw the cat into the sprinkler. It doesnï¿½t disguise itself otherwise, content to remain the antique liquid-breeze that hangs from lamp-posts and skyscrapers, the magnolia trees. It is the cloud that has passed in its sleep, the dew that has not yet lived, the acrid breath mint of the honeysuckle plant. It seldom moves but in sleepy pulls and heaves, reeling in slow-motion like a sweet-sick drunk as it stirs the insects from their suspended places and moves them, along with seeds, around parked cars and into window panes, gently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way night moves around a sleeping boy,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;soft,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;static,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;dream,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;under a canopy in heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Continuing Story of Danny, Princess of America</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/the-continuing-story-of-danny-princess-of-america/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/the-continuing-story-of-danny-princess-of-america/</id>
    <published>2003-08-06T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2015-12-03T23:59:00-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It was not altogether Danny’s fault&lt;/strong&gt; that the infamous Winchester Nine had settled in his house. He just remembered waking up that morning to the sound of silverwares and tea cups clincking wealthily in the parlor area. As he put on his glasses and removed his sleeping Cinta from his head, he could have sworn he heard the muffled sound of men speaking about grocery shopping. “Grocery shopping,” thought Danny, “that’s what I forgot to put on my ‘to-do’ list yesterday.” But it was too late for that now; he had mysterious figures sitting in the parlor sipping tea and discussing the rising and falling price of vegetables. Mysterious figures wearing black cloaks, swarthy burlap robes, and grim weapons strapped with blackened leather to their sides; Danny knew this because he was now standing in the middle of the floor, confused at the appearance of the Nine men. A stray thunder cloud sounded ominously from the rain on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“So hey. What’s up, guys?” said Danny quite smoothly, considering. The clatter of the teacups ceased as did the horrible muttering that issued from the monstrously wrinkled faces. There were 17 shiny, beady eyes directed at Danny in all of his yellow bathrobed splendor. A lune from the neighboring rainforest gave a lonesome cry that could be heard, if ever so imperceptibly, from the parlor of Danny’s house. The infamous Winchester Nine, serial killers and plunderers, all rose from the lacey graves of their chiffon-laden ottomans and put their teacups on the floor. Silently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“&lt;strong&gt;All hail Danny, Princess of America!&lt;/strong&gt;” they proclaimed in a grim and fierce voice that sounded as one. Danny remained in his place with his hands resting in the nestles of his bathrobe pockets. He adjusted his glasses and then he scratched his head. Surely this could not be reality. Perhaps he was dreaming yet. The Winchester Nine still stood facing him with unreasonably cold and unfriendly faces and their hands in a saluted position. As it turns out, it was reality and Danny was made the supervisor of the rotten criminal gang which eventually lead to his becoming the godfather of the entire French mafia which in turn lead to his untimely demise as a French aristocrat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rain came slowly at first, and then it gradually increased to hurricane-like proportions.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Like Antennas to Heaven</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/diaryland/like-antennas-to-heaven/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/diaryland/like-antennas-to-heaven/</id>
    <published>2003-08-06T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2015-12-03T23:54:45-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why do you keep feeling around in the sand&lt;/strong&gt; if you know there are poisonous crabs?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s time for a milk break, don’t you think?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
